Youtube subtitles download by mo.dbxdb.com
I can't believe this is my job right now
I'm barrel and for this episode of
around the world I'm trying something a
little different
a few weeks ago I made this story about
noodles
and in it I said I'm not doing instant
noodles that is a whole other episode
and if you want that one let me know
turns out you wanted that episode
so I had to think I couldn't film in a
Noodle Factory and it also didn't seem
that interesting to film in a Noodle
Factory
but
I had a kind of fun idea
I asked on YouTube how you guys liked to
prepare instant noodles where you lived
and the response was crazy
totally crazy
so I went through the responses and I
picked out eight that I wanted to try
myself
I went shopping
and I'm going to prepare eight of your
recipes from eight countries to see the
different ways that people prepare
instant noodles around the world
so this is the instant noodle episode
[Music]
the first noodle dish we're trying is
from Brazil
it's a simple recipe two ingredients
instant noodles and soft cheese so I'm
going to boil the noodles
once they're ready drain most of the
water add the seasoning packet add some
of the soft cheese stir stir stir
and then
[Music]
okay so this is kind of like a tomatoey
cheesy
hmm
it's really good
the noodles are really good they kind of
remind me of Top Ramen noodles
the Tomato flavor is really interesting
I've never had that one before
and the cheese is like
it doesn't taste like any cheese I've
ever had before
it tastes like
[Music]
it's like really
savory
this one's really great the ingredients
were not so easy to come by in U.S but I
found them
this next recipe came from Nigeria it
uses indomie noodles onions tomatoes
peppers and they recommended an egg on
top
so just chop up all the vegetables cook
them
boil the noodles
add the flavoring combine them all and
top with the egg
this one looks really good
kind of have to
break the yoga
totally different flavor than the last
noodle dish
and it is really good
it's like a very springy noodle
I like the Simplicity of this recipe
a little spicy very creamy the onions
are great
pepper is great tomatoes grapes
the egg yolk
it makes it creamier they said you could
add it or don't add it who doesn't want
to add an egg and this is a totally
totally satisfying dish
this next dish comes from Italy
there's chicken flavored instant noodles
a can of tuna cheese tomato avocado and
soy sauce
so you're gonna boil the noodles
drain most of the water add the flavor
packet add the cheese a can of drained
tuna fish and then top it with avocado
tomato and lastly a bit of soy sauce
this one was the most work so far a lot
of ingredients I actually really had to
follow the recipe
smells really good it's totally
different than anything I would ever
think to do with instant noodles
okay
the soy sauce is actually a really nice
touch on top it's got like an
interesting saltiness
it's funny it's totally growing on me
it's definitely got a heaviness and the
tomatoes do a really good job of
lightening that between the cheese and
the tuna and just you know the pasta
it's funny because in the person's note
they said trust me it's delicious all
right
[Music]
this submission came from Nepal and it's
why my noodles with onion tomato Ginger
lime juice and green chili you're gonna
mash up the noodles
cut up your vegetables
put them in a bowl add the noodles to
the Bowl put in some lime juice add the
seasoning packet and you're done
[Music]
okay this is the first instant noodle
dish that did not require any cooking
which I'm pretty excited about
[Music]
there's a freaking kick
I'm sweating
the tomato is nice it helps break down
the spice a little bit the lime juice
definitely a plus more than just
softening the noodles it definitely
helps a little bit with the heat
adding the green chili on top of the
spice packet that was a bold move
I'm really sweating
oh
I feel this would be really good with a
beer
that's really good
I like it
this recipe was a submission from
Trinidad and Tobago for this one I
needed spicy instant noodles so I just
added Sriracha KFC fried chicken and bok
choy take the skin off the chicken and
cook it so I put it in my air fryer
take the meat off of the bones your
hands are going to get really greasy put
that in a pot with the flavor packet
and some water let it boil add the bok
choy stems cook them for a bit add the
leafy part cook that for a bit and then
add the noodles put it in a bowl and
then you're gonna top it with the crispy
chicken skin
fabulous
I mean
this one's pretty extra it's also
beautiful
right
wow Honestly though that crispy chicken
skin
game changer
not even kidding if you serve me this in
a restaurant I would be like yeah this
tastes great
is that what Fried Chicken does
the noodles are Top Ramen had them
before I think adding the Sriracha
totally worked to make it spicy because
it's got a kick
also having the big pieces of chicken in
here is a delay
this is like elevated chicken soup the
soft noodles you have the leafy greens
the crunchy chicken
there's just like
it's a party
glad I got invited
this recipe was submitted from Indonesia
you need indomie noodles a bit of flour
egg scallion onion cheese and chicken
stock powder you're gonna cook the
noodles
rinse them in cold water add the
seasoning packet to the noodles chop up
the vegetables add the egg and the flour
and the chicken stock mix it all
together
don't pay so much attention to the
monitor that you spill all the noodles
and have to start again
make little pancakes fry them and then
top with a bit of melted cheese
well this one was definitely a lot of
work
foreign
that is an absolute Delight it's salty
and it's crispy and it's soft I love the
idea of taking instant noodles and
making these pancakes
the big chunks of onion in it are really
great the noodles just become a part of
the batter almost and the cheese is
great on top like it's fun but you don't
need it either I think I might eat one
more
I'm just gonna finish up
all right
this recipe was submitted from India
so for this dish you need Maggie
tomatoes onions peppers a little bit of
ghee and paneer put some ghee in the pan
add the vegetables add the chopped
paneer
a little bit of salt cover it
then you're gonna add noodles and some
water
cook it uncovered
and you're done
okay
this one smells really good
hot
the flavoring for these noodles
totally different flavor than any of the
other noodles I've tried
there's a similar base between this and
the Nigerian dish
but I cooked it with a little bit of
ghee
and so that adds a nice little flavor
kick and then the paneer is really nice
it's chewy and it's creamy and these
noodles are very bouncy
that's a good bite
and the Maggie flavoring is just really
good
in the great debate of why my noodles
versus Maggi noodles I feel like these
are two totally different noodles
the noodles taste totally different I
couldn't necessarily compare them
[Music]
this last recipe is a submission from
Singapore it uses ramyan cheese egg milk
scallion and chili flakes start by
cooking the noodles in milk
add some cheese add the flavor packets
add the chili flakes and then you're
gonna crack an egg and cover the pot
garnish with scallions
all right
this one smells luxurious
okay there's a lot to unpack here
this recipe is instantly comforting the
flavor packet for this is spicy but then
the cheese and the Egg combine
to make it really creamy
I've never cooked noodles and milk
before wow Game Changer really good when
you crack the egg in here the egg white
kind of cooks inside the noodles so you
get these pockets of egg white which is
really fun
man if I had known this recipe in
college
I would have been a happy happy student
wow this was such an amazing week not
only were your dishes delicious but they
were inventive
I knew that instant noodles were a
universal food but I had no idea how
customizable they could be and seeing
all the recipes from around the world
just really opened my mind
I'm going to put a link below so that
you can see the thread and look through
all the other recipes because I highly
recommend you try some of them I'm
obviously going to also include the
recipes that I cooked in the description
and if you have any other recipes please
leave them in the comments because I'm
converted I want to try more of them now
I also really enjoyed this experience of
trying to use different foods here at my
house because it shows that all of these
dishes are attainable you don't have to
necessarily travel to those countries to
get a taste of them so maybe I'll try it
again I don't know what do you think is
there another food I should do this with
that's kind of all I got
go try some of those noodle dishes you
will not be disappointed I promise
[Music]
Subtitles End: mo.dbxdb.com